Hello.
こんにちは
It's cute.
可愛いですね
thank you.
ありがとうございます
Your face is so small.
顔、ちっちゃいね
This is often said.
よく言われます
Are you told?
言われる?
Yes, it is said.
はい、言われます
I was surprised at how small it was.
小さすぎてびっくりしました
yes.
はい
Maybe I shouldn't ask.
聞いちゃいけないかもしれない
May I ask your age?
年齢聞いてもいいですか?
Yes, now age...
はい、今、年齢...
very soon?
もう すぐ?
Yes, soon.
はい、もうすぐ
Is school fun?
学校楽しい?
School is so much fun.
学校すごい楽しいです
What do you enjoy?
どんなことが楽しい?
There's a cultural festival going on, so that kind of thing.
なんか文化祭があるから、そういうのとか
I also enjoy the sports festival and being a professor.
あと は体育祭とか、教授が楽しいです
Oh, is that so?
あ、 そうなんですか?
yes.
はい
Do you have a boyfriend?
彼氏とかいるの?
I have a boyfriend.
彼氏います
Oh, are you there?
あ、いるの?
Yes, I have a boyfriend and we went to a fireworks festival the other day.
はい、彼氏いて、この前花火大会に行ってきました
Yeah, that's fine.
ええ、いいじゃん
yes.
はい
Did he wear a yukata or something?
彼、浴衣とか着たの?
Yes, I wore a yukata.
はい、浴衣で着ました
Wow, it looks really good on you.
うわー、めっちゃ似合いそうだね
yes.
はい
How long have you been dating your boyfriend?
彼氏とはさ、どのくらい付き合ってるの?
I've been with my boyfriend for 3 months.
彼氏とは3ヶ月です
Oh, is that so?
あ、そうなの?
yes.
はい
Which one did you confess to?
どっちから告白したの?
Oh, from my boyfriend.
あ、彼氏から
Have you been confessed?
告白されたの?
Yes, I was confessed.
はい、告白されました
Hey, why did you think we should date?
へー、なんで付き合おうかなと思ったの?
I also really liked it, and I was able to be both.
私もすごい好きで、両方になれたので、
I loved it at first.
私から最初好きでした
Ah, that's right.
あ、そうなんだ
yes.
はい
Ah, it's sour.
あ、酸っぱいね
yes.
はい
What is a boyfriend?
彼氏とは何?
Well, what about that?
まだじゃあ、そういうこととかは?
My boyfriend and I held hands at that fireworks display.
彼氏とは、あの花火大会で手繋ぎました
Oh, did you hold hands?
あ、手繋げた?
We held hands.
手繋がりました
Eh, neutralized?
え、中和した?
It's not neutralized.
中和してないです
Oh, you haven't?
あ、してないの?
Yes, not yet.
はい、まだないです
How many people have experience?
経験人数は何人ある?
Ah, not yet.
あ、まだないです
picture!?
え!?
Ah, zero people.
あ、ゼロ人です
What, you don't have any experience?
え、経験ないの?
No.
ないです
Seriously?
マジで?
yes.
はい
picture?
え?
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
It was a bit new to me.
ちょっと初耳だったね
Yes, no.
はい、ないです
How much contact do you have with men?
男の人と接触はどこまであります?
Ah, there's a reason why we held hands.
あ、手繋いだ理由はあります
Is that all?
それだけ?
Yes, that's right.
はい、そうです
What about kissing?
キスしたりとかは?
Ah, not yet.
あ、まだない
Not yet.
まだないです
Is that so?
そうなの?
yes.
はい
Wait, do you mean that men never see you naked?
ちょっとね、男の人になんか裸見られたりとかもないってことは?
I still have my father, though.
まだ、お父さんもあるけど
Are you interested?
興味はあったりするの?
I'm not completely interested, but I think it's a little scary and embarrassing.
興味はなくはないけど、ちょっと怖いし恥ずかしいかなって思
I'm here.
います
Wow, that sounds good.
う いういしいね
thank you.
ありがとうございます
Is it good?
ういういしいですか?
Yes, that's how delicious it is today.
今日はそう、そんなういういしいね
I thought I'd like to take some pictures of my body,
ちょっと 体を撮りたいなと思って、
I suddenly turned the camera around like this.
急にこんなカメラ回しちゃって
it's okay.
大丈夫です
Are you nervous?
緊張してるよね?
I'm nervous.
緊張してます
I agree.
そうだね
It's a little small.
ちょっと小さいんだね
This is dangerous.
やばいじゃん、これ
Is it dangerous?
やばいですか?
This is terrible.
やばいよ
You'll get arrested just by being together.
一緒にいるだけで捕まっちゃうよね
Yes, you will be arrested.
はい、捕まっちゃいますね
What should I do?
どうしよう
That's scary.
怖いなぁ
It doesn't stop.
止まらないもん
The camera will keep rolling.
カメラは回し続けちゃうよ
Yes, I understand.
はい、わかりました
It's okay, I won't show it to anyone, so it's okay.
大丈夫、誰にも見せないから大丈夫
It's a hobby.
趣味でね
Yes, it's okay.
はい、大丈夫です
May I?
いいですか?
That's scary.
怖いね
It's curvy, after all, it's a flower.
プリプリだね、やっぱりお花が
My hair is smooth.
髪はサラサラだしね
I'm getting my hair done.
髪は整えてます
Your hands are really sweaty.
すごい手汗かいてるじゃん
I'm a little nervous.
ちょっと緊張してて
Were you nervous?
緊張した?
Yes, I'm nervous.
はい、緊張してます
Hey, is this okay?
ちょっとこれ、大丈夫なの?
You might get a little angry.
ちょっと怒られちゃうかもしれない
Is it okay?
大丈夫かな?
it's okay.
大丈夫です
What is this?
こうやって何?
Does this exist?
これはあるの?
There is this.
これはあります
That's right.
そうなんだ
My hands are sweaty.
手汗がすごいね
My hands.
手が
I see.
そうか
You said you've never been hurt.
傷したことないって言ってたね
Yes, never.
はい、ことないです
I want to try it.
してみたいなって
I'm definitely nervous.
やっぱ緊張します
It's better to experience that kind of thing first.
そういうのはね、先に経験してた方がいいんだよ
Is it okay?
いいんですか?
oh yeah.
そうそう
Hey, would you like to try it?
ちょっとさ、やってみる?
Yes, I understand.
はい、わかりました
Is it okay?
いいの?
I'm a little nervous.
ちょっと緊張する
How far will you go today?
今日どこまでやるんですか?
It's a skin-like face.
肌顔ね
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
I'm nervous.
緊張します
Let's decorate your lips.
唇、飾ってみようか
I'm nervous.
緊張します
First Keys.
ファーストキーズ
It was taken away.
取られちゃいました
I'm nervous.
緊張します
This isn't actually a kiss.
これは 実 はキスじゃないんだよ
Is that so?
そうなんですか?
It's different.
違うんだよ
You don't know, right?
わかんないでしょ?
I don't know.
わかんないです
Take out the bottom.
下を出してごらん
It's really long.
すっごい長い
It's been a long time.
長いことやっちゃったね
I was surprised.
びっくりしました
Were you surprised?
びっくりした?
how was it?
どうだった?
My hands were also throbbing.
手もドキドキしました
did?
した?
It felt good, didn't it?
ちょっと、気持ちよかったでしょ?
This is a kiss.
これがキスなんだよ
Just give me a massage.
ちょっと、 マッサージして
It's my first time being touched.
触られるのも初めてです
Seriously?
マジで?
yes.
はい
I'm glad.
喜んでんじゃん
Is it okay?
いいの?
Is it okay if I'm the first?
俺が初めてでいいの?
I might get angry.
怒られちゃうかもしれない
Like a safe coat?
金庫コートみたいな?
Will you get angry?
怒られちゃう?
I might get angry.
怒られちゃうかもしれない
You'd better practice.
練習してたほうがいいよ
practice?
練習?
It's soft.
柔らかいね
Is something hitting your back?
背中に何か当たってる?
I'm right.
当たってます
Is it correct?
当たってる?
What does it feel like?
どんな感じ?
hard.
硬い
hard?
硬い?
Have you seen the real thing?
実物は見たことある?
My father is still my only choice.
まだ、お父さんのしかない
My father is the only one.
お父さんのしかないです
Really?
本当に?
Isn't that also a lie?
それも嘘でしょ?
Well then, my brother's too.
じゃあ、弟のも
My brother's too?
弟のも?
It's a little embarrassing to have such a beautiful body.
ちょっとさ、 この 綺麗な体みたいな 恥ずかしいです
You can take a picture a little higher.
ちょっと上、撮れてるね
I was only able to take a picture of the top.
上だけ撮れちゃいました
good?
いい?
That's fine.
いいです
Wow, you're so excited.
すごい、 ハキハキしてるね
good.
いい
sexy.
セクシー
That's sexy.
セクシーだね
It's not big though.
大きくはないですけど
That's amazing.
すごいよ
During early childhood.
初育中の
He's in early childhood.
初育中だね
It's big.
大きいじゃん
Is it big?
大きいんですか?
The girls in your class are big, right?
クラスの女の子は大きいでしょ?
No, I wish we could grow a little bit more from here.
いや、 ここからもうちょっと 大きくなれたらいいんですけど
TRUE?
本当?
I'm touching it normally, but is it okay?
普通に触っちゃってるけど大丈夫?
it's okay.
大丈夫です
It's super soft.
超柔らかいじゃん
Is it soft?
柔らかいですか?
Super soft.
超柔らかい
That's amazing.
すごいね
Shall we stand for a moment?
ちょっと立ってみようか
I want to see the bottom too.
下も見たいからさ
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
Show me below too.
下の下にも見せてよ
What, are you flipping the pages?
え、めくるんですか?
Show me, show me.
見せてよ見せてよ
Just a little bit.
ちょっとだけ
Just a little bit?
ちょっとだけ?
Super beautiful.
超綺麗
Is it beautiful?
綺麗ですか?
So beautiful.
めっちゃ綺麗
Can I hide it?
隠していいですか?
No, no, no.
ダメダメダメ
Like this.
こんな
It seems quite adult-like.
結構大人っぽいね
yes.
はい
It's far away.
遠 いんだね
that's right.
そうです
Hair removal was still expensive and my mom said no, so I turned around.
脱毛まだ高くて お母さんがダメって言われて 後ろ向いてさ、
Show me your butt too.
お尻も見せてよ
Are you going to show me your butt too?
お尻も見せるんですか?
Yes, I understand.
はい、わかりました
It's ticklish.
くすぐったいです
tickles.
く すぐったい
It's super beautiful.
超綺麗だよ
amazing.
すごい
She's so curvy, after all, she's young.
プリプリだね、やっぱ若いから
Is it true?
本当ですか?
Get on your knees on the chair.
椅子の上にさ、膝つけてさ
Four times as many.
4つの倍にさ
Is it true?
本当ですか?
Yeah, yeah.
そうそうそう
Stick your butt out.
お尻さ、突き出して
4 times.
4つの倍に
Yeah, yeah.
そうそうそう
You look embarrassing.
恥ずかしい格好してるね
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしいです
Hey.
ね え
Are these rather adult-looking pants open?
この結構大人っぽい パンツ開いてるの?
Yes, I bought some underwear with my mom.
はい、お母さんと 下着買ってきました
Is that so?
そうなの?
What an ass.
なんだお尻
She has cute legs.
可愛い足してる
Is it cute?
可愛いですか?
It's toned up, quite a bit.
引き締まってるね、結構ね
Something like that?
なんか、あれ?
Do you have any club activities?
部活とかやってるの?
I do club activities and track and field.
部活、陸上やってる
I'm doing track and field.
陸上やってるんだ
Are you running?
走ってる?
I'm running.
走ってます
I got hurt a little bit.
ちょっと怪我しちゃって
I felt like I was on vacation.
休み気味だったんですけど
Wow, it's kind of tight.
すごい、なんか引き締まってる
Are you toned?
引き締まってますか?
Do you understand?
分 かる?
Are you toned?
引 き締まってますか?
Well then, look, it's hot now, isn't it?
じゃあさ、もうほら、 暑いでしょ?
It might be hot.
暑いかもしれない
Here?
ここでですか?
Usually, I wear a uniform.
普段はね、 制服だもんね
Uniform, sailor suit.
制服、セーラー服です
General section.
普 段
Are you going to take it all off now?
今全部脱ぐんですか?
That's right, I don't think I'll ever come this far.
そうっすね、もうここまで来ないかな
Please wear your uniform next time.
今度制服着てきてよ、じゃあ
got it.
わかりました
That's fine.
いいですよ
Very stylish.
めっちゃスタイルいい
Do you like the style?
スタイルいいですか?
After all, track and field girls are a little toned.
や っぱり陸上女子って、 ちょっと引き締まってるね
I've been eating a little too much lately, and something came out.
最近ちょっと食べすぎて、 なんか出てきたんですけど
Not at all.
全然じゃん
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしいです
soft.
柔らかい
Is it soft?
柔らかいですか?
Are you embarrassed?
恥ずかしい?
Super soft.
超柔らかい
Let's sit down for a while, see you later.
ちょっと座っちゃおうか、またね
One more time.
もう一回
Has your boyfriend seen it too?
彼氏も見たことは?
Not yet.
まだない
My brother saw it.
弟は見たんだ
You're watching it at home.
家で見てるよね
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
恥ずかしいです
Can I see it?
見ていいの?
Just a little bit.
少しだけ
Are you young?
若いですか?
I want to take a good look at it.
よく見たいね
Are you going to take it off?
外すんですか?
I haven't heard of it being removed.
外すって聞いてない
I might hide it.
隠しちゃうかもしれないです
If only I had hidden it.
隠しちゃってたら
sorry.
ごめんなさい
Why are you hiding it?
なんで隠してるの?
I'm embarrassed.
恥ずかしくて
Are you embarrassed?
恥ずかしいの?
Why?
どうして?
Because I've never shown it.
見せたことないから
Did your brother see it?
弟は見たんですか?
My brother has seen it before.
弟は見たことあるんですけど
Don't you want to do something like this with your brother?
弟とこんなことしたくないか
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
恥ずかしいですね
So beautiful.
すっごい綺麗
Is it beautiful?
綺麗ですか?
Pink...I'll hide it again.
ピンク...また隠しちゃう
I'll hide it for a while.
ちょっと隠します
Growing...
成長中の...
It's growing.
成長中です
yes.
はい
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしいな
You'll always be smiling.
ず っと笑顔でいてくれるね
The only thing missing is a smile.
笑顔だけが足りないです
That's a good thing.
いいことだよ
Soft.
柔らか
Is it true?
本当ですか?
You can touch it all the time.
ずっと触ってられる
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしいです
I want to touch it for the rest of my life.
一生触ってたい
No.
ダメです
It's ticklish.
くすぐったいです
Does it feel ticklish?
くすぐったい感じがする?
It feels ticklish.
くすぐったい感じがします
It's ticklish.
くすぐったいです
Taste?
味見?
Me, absolutely.
私、絶対です
It's difficult.
難しいよ
delicious.
美味しい
Is it delicious?
美味しいですか?
Young people, young people.
若者、若者
difficult.
難しい
difficult?
難しい?
yes.
はい
It's my first time and I'm really nervous.
初めてですごく緊張しちゃう
Hey, suddenly.
ねえ、急に
I was told no.
ねえって言われてね
Look back at this later, what do you think I'll do?
これ後で見返して、 俺何すると思う?
What, what are you going to do?
え、何するんですか?
It's a boy.
男の子だ
Oh, do you understand that?
あ、そういうの分かるの?
I understand.
分かります
I understand that.
それは分かります
Did you learn it at school?
学校で習った?
I didn't learn it at school.
学校では習ってない
Roll it up a little.
ちょっと巻きよ
Just wrap both.
ちょっと両方巻きよ
yes.
はい
It's not pretty.
綺麗じゃないです
It's not like shaving your head at all.
全然髪剃りなんだね
I'm embarrassed because I'm not that pretty.
あんな綺麗じゃないから恥ずかしい
That's amazing.
すごいね
It's beautiful.
綺麗だよ
Is it true?
本当ですか?
Ah, that's embarrassing.
あ、恥ずかしい
tickles.
くすぐったい
It tastes like sweat.
汗の味がする
Ah, that's embarrassing.
あ、恥ずかしい
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしいです
Please don't say that.
そういうこと言わないでください
It's delicious.
美味しいよ
yes.
はい
Are you used to it yet?
もう慣れっ子?
not at all.
全然
It's just what I taught you earlier.
さっき教えたもんだったばっかりだから
Aren't you used to it?
慣れたんじゃない?
I'm not used to it at all.
全然慣れてないです
Really?
本当に?
not at all.
全然
cute.
可愛い
I want to be her.
彼女にしたい
No.
ダメです
Please make me your boyfriend.
彼氏にしてください
No.
ダメです
Seriously?
マジか
But today I wanted to do a lot of things that my boyfriend didn't do.
でも今日彼氏がやってないことをいっぱいしたいなと思って
yes.
はい
Just a little bit,
ちょっとさ、
tickles.
く すぐったい
These are beautiful feet.
この綺麗な足だね
Is it beautiful?
綺麗ですか?
Lift your legs up, legs,
足を上げてさ、 足、
It's embarrassing.
恥 ずかしい
恥ずかしい
Because it's hidden.
隠れてるからね
Let me open it up a little.
ちょっと開いてもらおう
Shika?
し っか
the law of nature.
り
Can I close it?
閉 じていいですか?
No.
ダメだよ
difficult.
難しい
A little hair is sticking out.
ちょっと毛がはみ出てる
Please don't look.
見ないでください
Have you ever touched it yourself?
ここさ、 自分で触ったりとかしたことある?
do not have.
ない
As much as possible.
できるだけ
Because there isn't.
ないから
There isn't.
ないよね
It's a strange feeling.
不思議な感覚です
A strange feeling?
不思議な感覚?
yes.
はい
It's really strange.
すごい不思議です
lie?
嘘?
tickles.
くすぐったい
Does it feel ticklish?
くすぐったい感じがする?
yes.
はい
I feel like I can't say anything.
なんとも言えない感じがします
That's right.
そうなんだ
Please do not take pictures close up.
近くで撮らないでください
It hurts.
痛いよ
How far do you look?
どこまで見るんですか?
Come on, show me.
ちょっとさ、 見せてよ
difficult.
難しい
Show me a little bit.
見せてよ、ちょっと
Are you going to take it off?
脱がすんですか?
Just a little bit.
ちょっとだけ
ちょっとだけですよ
Can I take this home?
これ 持って帰っていい?
No.
ダメです
Please don't go home after seeing it.
見て帰らないでください
It's so beautiful.
めちゃくちゃ綺麗だね
Is it beautiful?
綺麗ですか?
It's growing, isn't it?
生えてるよね
How far should I open it?
どこまで開くのもいいんですか?
yes.
はい
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしいです
恥ずかしい
It was born for the first time.
初めて生えてきた
I don't remember.
覚えてない
About junior high school students.
中学生くらい
I guess I'm a junior high school student.
中学生かな
Is that so?
そんなの?
amazing.
すごい
It's close.
近いです
close?
近い?
Super beautiful.
超綺麗
Maybe I'll take a closer look in bed.
ちょっと、 ベ ッドで よく見ちゃおうかな
Isn't it the end?
終わりじゃないんですか?
Because I can't see it at all yet.
まだ全然見えてないから
You've already seen it, haven't you?
もう見たじゃないですか
yes.
はい
Because it's my first time.
初めてだから
get nervous?
緊 張する?
Is it hitting your waist?
腰に当たっている?
yes.
はい
I don't want to say it because it's embarrassing.
恥ずかしいから言いたくない
What is correct?
どんなのが当たってる?
long.
長い
long?
長い?
The long one is correct.
長いのが当たってる
yes.
はい
That's a plump butt.
プリプリのお尻だね
It's so soft, so soft.
プリプリだ、プリプリ
Is it impossible?
無理ですか?
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
How far should I open it?
どれくらい開けばいいんですか?
I've had enough.
もういっぱい
yes.
そう
That's naughty.
やらしいね
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
恥ずかしいよね
But, it's so beautiful.
でもね、すっごい綺麗
Is it beautiful?
綺麗ですか?
It's so beautiful.
すっごい綺麗だよ
Can I hide it?
隠していいですか?
No.
ダメ
No good?
ダメかって
It was so cute.
めちゃくちゃ可愛かった
close.
近い
It's close.
近 い です よ
So beautiful.
すっごい綺麗
Just a little bit,
ちょっとさ、
liquid liquid liquid
液 体が 液体が
Well, it's ticklish.
さ、 くすぐったいんだ
It feels kind of strange.
なんか不思議な感じがします
It feels strange.
不思議な感じがします
Does it feel strange?
不思議な感じがする?
Open it.
開いてごらん
open?
開く?
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
Can I close it?
閉じていいですか?
No.
ダメだよ
Your nails are cute.
ネイルが可愛いね
I can do my nails however I want.
ネイルとか自由にやっていいので
It's okay.
いいんだ
perhaps.
多分
perhaps?
多分?
But it was stylish.
でもおしゃれしたよね
I want to get my nails done.
ネ イルしたい
Can I close it?
閉じてもいいですか?
No.
ダメです
Is it no good?
ダメなんですか?
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
cute.
可愛い
I've never touched it.
触ったことないんだよね
Please show me a little.
ちょっと見せてくれ
Wow, that's tiny.
うわ、ちっちゃい
Do you know what these beans are called?
このお豆さ、なんていうか知ってる?
I don't know.
わかんない
tickles.
くすぐったい
What does it feel like to be touched?
触られたらどんな感じ?
It feels strange.
不思議な感じがします
Does it feel strange?
不思議な感じ?
It's like being massaged.
マッサージされてるみたい
I'm giving you a massage.
マッサージしてるよ
Does it feel good?
気持ちいい感じがする?
It feels good.
気持ちいい感じします
Have you heard of it?
聞いたことある?
yes.
はい
it hurts.
痛い
yes.
はい
It's your first time.
初めてだよね
yes.
はい
It hurts.
痛いです
it hurts?
痛い?
yes.
はい
It's so tight I can't get in.
すごいきつくて入っていかない
It hurts.
痛いです
痛いよ
it hurts?
痛い?
yes.
はい
It came out.
出てきた
You can let go.
手を離していいよ
yes.
はい
It hurts a little.
ちょっと痛いです
It hurts but it feels strange.
痛いけど不思議な感じがします
Does it feel strange?
不思議な感じがする?
yes.
はい
Hey, you should give me a massage.
ちょっとさ、マッサージここさ、 しておいた方がいいよ
That's no good.
ダメですね
yes.
はい
I feel kind of nervous.
なんかツキツキします
I feel prickly.
ツキツキします
It feels strange.
不思議な感じがします
Does it feel weird?
変な感じ?
It feels weird.
変な感じがします
It's like a tsukitsuki.
ツキツキみたい
Tsukitsuki.
ツキツキ
It feels weird, right?
変な感じするでしょ?
It feels weird.
変な感じします
I don't know what to say.
何て言ったらいいか分かんないです
It feels strange.
不思議な感じがします
Does it feel strange?
不思議な感じがする?
It's like it tickles and it feels good.
くすぐった気持ちいいみたいな
It tickles and it feels good.
くすぐった気持ちいい
yes.
はい
That's what it feels like.
そんな感じがします
It's so strange.
すごい不思議な
It's tingling.
ズンズンします
Does it make you tingle?
ズンズンする?
Something amazing is coming out.
すごいなんか、 やっぱなんか出てきてる
It hurts.
痛いです
It's tough.
きついね
It hurts.
痛いです
I won't go in.
入っていかないね
I'm not going in.
入っていかないです
This is a little harsh.
ちょっときついね、これ
It's a strange feeling, throbbing.
不思議な感覚、ズキズキします
I'll go with one.
1本なら入っていくね
It's throbbing and it's a strange feeling.
ズキズキして、 不思議な感覚です
That's why it feels like it's melting.
だから、 とろけそうな感じがします
Does it feel like that?
そうな感じがするの?
Does it feel good?
気 持ちいいってこと?
I don't know if it feels good, but it's throbbing.
気持ちいいのか分かんないけど、 ズ キズキします
It used to hurt a little while ago, but now it doesn't hurt as much.
さっきまで痛かったんですけど、 今はあんまり痛くないです
It's a great live broadcast.
すっごい実況中継してくれる
It's my first time.
初めてだからね
Tell me what you don't understand.
分かんないことばらけて
You'll be surprised.
びっくりしちゃうよね
It was my first time.
初めてすぎて
That's amazing.
すごいね
Are you going to taste it?
味見するんですか?
I want to make it.
作ったいんです
It tastes sweet.
甘い味がするよ
Is it true?
本当ですか?
That's naughty.
やらしいね
Were you surprised?
びっくりした?
Yes, I was surprised.
はい、びっくりしました
Just sit straight.
正座して座ってことね
Are you sitting straight?
正座ですか?
Were you surprised when I touched you?
触られてびっくりしたでしょ?
I was surprised.
びっくりしました
Have you ever seen it?
見たことあるんだっけ?
No.
ないです
My father and younger brother are the only ones.
お父さんと弟のしかないです
Have you ever touched it?
触ったことは?
I've never touched it.
触ったことないです
It's a little scary.
ちょっと怖い
I'll try touching it.
触ってみます
How should I touch it?
どう触ったらいいですか?
It was my first time touching it.
初めて触りました
初 めて触りました
It feels strange.
不思議な感じです
Is this also a strange feeling?
これも不思議な感じ?
It feels strange because I don't have it.
自分にないから不思議な感じです
That's right.
そうだよね
I don't think so.
ない思います
What do you mean you've seen it?
見たことあるってことは?
yes.
はい
I think it's different from the current situation.
今の状態と違うと思うからさ
I agree.
そうですね
Please watch carefully.
しっかりと見ててね
Yes, I understand.
はい、わかりました
I saw it for the first time.
初めて見ました
I can't look at it directly.
あまり直視できないです
First time seeing it?
初めて見た?
I saw it for the first time.
初めて見ました
I want you to see it up close.
近くで見てほしい
This is how it is.
こうなってるんですね
I saw it for the first time.
初めて見ました
It feels strange.
不思議な感じです
This is how it is.
こうなってるんですね
So?
それで?
Do it like this.
こうやってね
yes.
はい
Move it?
動かして?
yes.
はい
Does it match?
合ってますか?
Shikoku?
四国?
It's right, it's right.
合ってる合ってる
Because you said it earlier.
さっき言ってたから
Does it feel good because the boy feels great when I do this?
こうすると 男の子すごい気持ちいいから 気持ちいいんですか?
If you have feelings or are excited, your excitement will expand.
気持ちがあったり 興奮してると興奮の 膨張しちゃってる
I'm surprised.
驚いてるね
Surprised.
びっくり
I think this is what's going on.
こうなってるんだと思って
You'll do it someday, right?
いつかやるでしょ?
Boyfriend or something.
彼氏とか
Will I do it?
や る のかな?
Just a little.
ちょっとさ
yes.
はい
Yes, there are things that feel better.
もっと気持ちいいことがあって はい
Could you please give it a try?
ペロリって してみてくれない?
yes.
はい
Wait and get nervous.
待って緊張する
Have you seen it?
見たことあるでしょ?
What do you have?
何があるんですか?
Something like this.
こういうの
There isn't.
ないよ
Please give me a lick.
ペロリってしてくれ
Can I do it anywhere?
どこにしてもいいんですか?
yes.
はい
Does it feel good?
気持ちいいですか?
air
気
It lasts a long time.
持 ちいい
Does it feel good?
気持ちいいですか?
difficult.
難しい
Lick it even more.
も っとペロペロして
yes.
はい
Does it feel good?
気持ちいいですか?
I'm a little embarrassed.
ちょっと照れちゃう
You're good at it, it's amazing.
上手だよ、すごい
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
This is it.
これでね
yes.
はい
Like this.
こうやって
Please add it.
加えてくれ
Are you adding it?
加えてるんですか?
Like that.
そうやって
Move it with your mouth.
口で動かしてくれ
No more.
これ以上だ
You're really good at it.
すっごい上手じゃん
I guess I'm not used to it yet.
まだ慣れてないかな
I don't know.
わか んない
What did you think?
どう思った?
It feels amazing.
すごい気持ちいい
TRUE?
本当?
First time making a hot pot?
初めての鍋?
yes.
はい
amazing.
すごい
It was my first time experiencing it.
初めて経験しちゃったね
It was my first experience.
初めて経験しました
Surprised?
びっくり?
Surprised.
びっくり
I'll tell you this.
これ教えてあげるね
Does it match?
合ってますか?
It's right, it's right.
合ってる合ってる
It fits.
合ってる
Look at the camera.
カメラ見てくれ
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
That's terrible.
やばいね
He said he was playing with me, and he started licking me again.
私と遊ぶってさ、 またペロってしてきた
yes.
はい
Something came out.
なんか出てきました
Where is it?
どこですか?
The one that came out.
出てきたやつ
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
Are you embarrassed?
恥ずかしい?
yes.
はい
My head is used to being licked.
頭のほうさ、ペロペロって慣れてます
Is this so?
こうですか?
Does it feel good?
気持ちいいんですか?
It feels good.
気持ちいいです
It's amazing because Pero is so soft.
すごいなんか、ペロが 柔らかいからさ
Is it soft?
柔 ら かいんですか?
yes.
はい
I couldn't stand it anymore.
我慢できなくなっちゃった
What should I do?
どうしよう
Shall we lie down?
横になろうか
Is it on the side?
横ですか?
It's full of strange things, isn't it?
不思議なことばっかりでしょ
Even if I'm not used to it, I don't understand it at all.
慣れてなくても、 全然わかんないです
You'll be surprised, all of a sudden.
びっくりしちゃうよね、急にね
Thank you for moving.
移れてくれてね
There are so many things you don't learn at school.
学校じゃ 習わないことばっかりだもんね
I don't learn it.
習わないです
Just a moment, here, if you do this,
ちょっとさ、 ここね、 こうするとさ、
It feels good.
気持ちいいんだ
Spread me out.
私広げて
good?
いい?
yes.
はい
It feels strange.
不思議な感じです
Because it didn't fit into my fingers.
指に入らなかったからね
yes.
はい
It feels strange.
不 思 議な感じがします
That's amazing.
すごいね
yes.
はい
But that's no good.
でもそれはダメです
wait a minute.
ちょっと待って
What?
何が?
It's still my first time, so it's still scary.
まだ初めてだから、 それはまだ怖い
what?
何?
Do you do this?
こうするの?
Not yet because I'm scared.
怖いから、まだ
Hey, I'm getting excited too.
ちょっとさ、 俺もさ、 興奮しちゃってさ、
Just get ahead of yourself, right?
先行っちゃうだけでしょ
yes.
はい
But it's scary.
でも怖いから
Please tell me your thoughts, I'd like to hear them.
ちょっと感想をさ、 聞きたいからさ、
yes.
はい
It hurts.
痛いです
I'd like you to tell me how it feels.
ちょっとどんな感じかさ、 教えてほしくて
Is it okay?
ちょっと いい?
If you just ask me what you think, that's it.
感想だけ聞いたら、 もう終わりでいいから
it hurts.
痛い
It's scary.
怖いです
Are you shaking?
震えてる?
Are you okay?
大丈夫?
yes.
はい
it's okay.
大丈夫です
It's just a little bit.
ちょっとだけだからね
It's a little scary.
ちょっと怖いです
copper?
どう?
But it's all over.
でも、 全然終わりだよ
Looks like it's over.
終わってそう
It hurts.
痛いです
yes.
はい
It's my first time, so it's scary.
初めてだから、 怖いです
But hey, it was in.
でもさ、 入ってったね
I was surprised that my finger didn't fit inside.
指入らなかったのに、 びっくりだね
What can I see?
何て見てもいい?
It's a little scary.
ちょっと怖い
It's not in there at all, so is it okay?
全然入ってないから、 大丈夫?
first time?
初めて?
Is this your first time entering it?
初めて入れたの?
It's my first time.
初めてです
I'm surprised.
びっくりです
It still hurts a little.
まだちょっと痛いんです
it hurts?
痛い?
yes.
はい
enter
入
Isn't that okay?
って いかない?
Don't go in at all?
全然入っていかない?
yes.
はい
What are you scared of?
何が怖いの?
It doesn't hurt.
痛くない
It'll be over soon.
すぐ終わるから
Fall down.
落ちて
It'll be over soon.
すぐ終わるから
What does it feel like?
どんな感じ?
It's coming in.
入っていってるね
It's starting to collapse.
潰れてきてるね
It hurts just a little.
ちょっとだけ痛い
Does it feel good?
気持ちいい?
Which one?
どっち?
it hurts.
痛い
Feels good.
気持ちいい
Does it feel good?
気持ちいいの?
This way.
こっちをさ
Open this here.
こっち開いてこな
Does it feel good?
気持ちいいですか?
It feels so good.
気持ちよすぎ
What is this?
何これ?
It feels so good though.
気持ちよすぎるんだけど
This is terrible.
やばいよ
A child who has been crushed.
潰れてきたっていう子
How's the pain?
痛みはどう?
It's better than before, It's okay.
さっきよりは、 さっきよりは、 大丈夫です
It's slimy.
ぬるぬるしてる
Feels good.
気持ちいい
copper?
どう?
it hurts.
痛い
It feels a little good.
ちょっと気持ちいい
That's amazing.
すごいね
It's slimy.
ぬるぬるしてる
It feels good.
気 持ちいい
It has collapsed.
潰れてきた
Because it hurts,
痛いから、
You had better study.
勉 強しといたほうがいいから
Are you studying?
勉強ですか?
Come on, get on top of me.
ちょっと上にさ、 俺の上に乗って
After all, it's track and field.
やっぱり陸上だから
Do you understand this?
これわかる?
Something like this.
こういうの
It's a little different, isn't it?
またちょっと違うでしょ
No.
違います
copper?
どう?
it hurts?
痛い?
It hurts just a little.
ちょっとだけ痛いです
Could you please straighten it?
まっすぐしてもらおうか
I'll move.
俺が動いてあげるね
yes.
はい
They say it feels good.
気 持 ちいいって言うんだよ
nostalgic?
懐かしい?
There are things like this too.
こういうのもあるからね
Were you surprised?
びっくりした?
Feels good.
気持ちいい
amazing.
すごい
Reach behind you and spread your legs.
後ろにさ、手を伸ばしてさ、 足を広げてもらおう
Now, let's move slowly on our own.
さあ、今度は自分で ゆっくり動いてみよう
Can you see the naughty part?
やらしい入っているところ、 そば見える?
It's difficult.
難しいです
It looks really good.
めちゃくちゃよく見えるよ
何個?
You can move really well.
すごい動けるね
Were you able to wash away the pain?
痛み洗いできた?
Yes, from before.
はい、さっきよりは
Wow, you've grown so much.
すごい、成長したね
Panpan.
パンパン
Just a little bit, yes.
ちょっとさ、 はい
Let me stick my butt out like before.
さっきみたいに、お尻を突き出してもらおう
Are you embarrassed by this look?
この格好が恥ずかしい?
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしいです
Let me take a look at this.
こっち見てもらおう
I can't see it at all.
まる見えないな
Please don't look.
見ないでください
Does that mean please take a look?
そういうことは、 見て くださいってこと?
No.
違います
It's tough, it's crazy.
きついね、めちゃくちゃ
Is it still different?
まだ違う?
yes.
はい
I'll take it slow.
ゆ っくりやるね
It's jiggling.
プルプルしてるね
Does it hurt a little?
ちょっと痛い?
yes.
はい
Are you nervous?
緊張してる?
Yes, I'm nervous
はい、緊張して
Masu.
ます
It feels really good though.
め ちゃくちゃ気持ちいいんだけど
It's tough.
きついもん
It's my first time being this hard.
こんなきついの初めてだよ、俺
amazing.
すごい
good?
いい?
amazing.
すごい
copper?
どう?
From before...
さっきよりは...
Does it feel good?
気持ちいい?
Does the pain feel good?
痛い気持ちいい?
TRUE?
本当?
It's my first time.
初めてだね
You're talented.
才能あるんだね
wait a minute.
ちょっと待って
Wow, that's terrible.
すごい、やばい
I just can't stand it.
ちょっと我慢できない
terrible.
やばい
や ばい
I can't stand it.
我慢できない
terrible.
やばい
Will it go up?
上がる?
Did you feel something?
何か感じた?
Is it warm?
温かいの?
This is my first time.
初めてか、こんな
If it's hard, it's okay.
ハードだったらもう大丈夫だよ
OK?
大丈夫ですか?
yes.
はい